So refreshing.
(Bukit Lawang, Indonesia)
The grass is longer here.
We're getting deeper into the jungle.
The grass is longer.
I see something...
that looks like a fern
from the Paleozoic era.
Like this.
You're right.
(They see unfamiliar plants.)
Ipu, I want to see that grass.
When we touch it...
When we touch it, it curls up.
It's not here.
Not here?
- Maybe we can look over there.
- Is that so?
We have it in Korea.
They don't have it here.
Maybe they haven't found it.
There's no way it doesn't grow here.
- One minute, please.
- Okay.
One minute?
- Are we done?
- Why?
- Is he going home?
- Let me pick some of those leaves.
He's going to pick that.
- What's that?
- Amazing.
Is he going to climb that tree?
Is he going to shake that tree
and knock something down?
(Jumping)
(Ipu climbs the tree.)
He's like Tarzan.
That's really cool.
- Seriously.
- That's awesome.
That's the way to live.
(Watching in awe)
(Skillfully picking a leaf)
You can tell that he loves this job.
That's really cool.
He probably doesn't see it as work.
It's like introducing your home.
A room tour.
He's giving us a room tour.
He took us on a room tour.
Ipu's room tour.
Do you know what this is for?
- Do you know?
- Is that sugarcane?
No.
- What is that?
- This can be used as a dye.
Smooth?
- Smooth?
- For painting?
You can dye things with this.
(They finally understand.)
Can I touch it?
- Maybe put it here.
- Okay.
Maybe here.
(Rubbing it on a white cloth)
(It dyes the cloth red!)
Is it some kind of pigment?
A natural dye!
(The more he rubs it,
the darker the color gets.)
It will stay until you get back to Korea.
Yes, I'm serious.
(The color holds up well!)
That's okay.
- Do you have another?
- Just one color?
One color.
That's so interesting.
It's like a colored pencil.
That's fascinating.
It's so much fun.
This room tour is fun.
- It's like a jungle adventure.
- I know.
This is not bad.
It's pretty good so far.
It's like a trekking route.
If we keep going,
- we'll see monkeys...
- Yes.
- and orangutans too, right?
- I think so.
The way to our lodging goes
through where orangutans live.
Here?
We're visiting the orangutans' home, then.
There isn't a designated area
where they live.
No. They just roam freely in the wild.
We can see them on our way to our place.
(The whole jungle is their home.)
It feels like this is
where the jungle starts.
I think we're entering the national park.
(Arriving at the entrance
of the national park)
Let's start trekking now.
Okay, trekking!
Let's go inside.
It's getting started.
That was just the intro so far.
Let's look for orangutans and monkeys.
- Okay!
Let's just do it!
Let's go.
I'm walking in lunges,
squeezing my glutes.
It's a little muddy here.
We're pretty used to mud now.
Right.
The elephant hotel was muddy too.
We're very familiar with Mr. Mud now.
- Mr. Mud?
- Yes.
Mr. Mud,
let's break up.
(A random skit)
I'm speechless.
Mr. Mud.
Mr. Mud, let's break up.
Mr. Mud, I'm going to study abroad.
Stop following me.
(Don't look for me.)
(Who are you?)
That's so funny.
Number Three seems to be struggling.
No, I'm good.
You look so tired from behind.
(She looks exhausted from behind.)
Number Three, are you okay?
Number Three isn't tired.
(The company commander is
disappointed in Number Three.)
I'm so glad...
that it's not blazing hot.
I agree.
If it was scorching hot,
- I would've run away.
- I know.
It's a real jungle.
(The slope gets steeper.)
Now it's uphill.
(Calling Ipu)
When did you start climbing trees?
Do you want to try?
No.
That's not what she meant.
Goodness.
Is he going to show us?
Here.
He's telling me to try.
(Pushing through the grass,
straight to a tree)
- Let's try it.
- I want to try climbing it.
- You might be good at it.
- I think so too.
You might be good.
(The expert shows an example.)
That looks like fun.
I've always wanted to climb a tree.
- Let's try it.
- Okay.
(Climbing the tree with bare hands)
Let's go!
Come up.
(He reached the top quickly.)
Me too.
Isn't there a limit
to how many people can climb the tree?
- Amazing!
- How is it?
You're climbing well.
It's fun.
How far up did he climb?
(Relaxed)
She's so good at climbing.
(She's already halfway up.)
- This is crazy.
- She's a monkey.
I'm so talented, right?
Be careful.
(She's talented in many ways.)
Let's go!
She's good at it.
(Singing)
(She's talented like a monkey.)
(She can dance while climbing a tree.)
Am I impressive?
I'll go down.
My lower body is so weak.
(Sian gave up while flailing around.)
Are you going to go down that way?
(Pulling)
Really?
(Tarzan)
That's cool.
This is his playground.
That's impressive.
(He's basically one with the tree.)
Will Harimu do that too?
She should just come down, just in case.
- Right.
- I'm scared for her.
Okay.
(One step down)
She's using her arms to climb down.
(Turning)
Watch out.
- Did you get any splinters?
- I'm good.
That was fun, like pole dancing.
Okay!
- Okay!
I shouldn't have done that.
My shoulder hurts.
It hurts?
I feel like it got a little twisted.
- She did her best,
- I couldn't do it.
but the talented one got
all our attention.
She didn't get enough attention.
I'm so talented, right?
She got the spotlight,
- Right.
- so I gave up and came down.
She did too well.
She totally stole the spotlight.
Jane!
Jane from "Tarzan."
Is he talking about Jane from "Tarzan?"
"Tarzan."
I think he liked it.
No, I'm a city girl.
(Getting ahead of herself)
City girls!
(The city girls' jungle trip continues.)
By the way,
I bet it feels so cool in the valley.
- Seriously.
- Right?
- I'd jump in.
- We don't even need bathing suits.
We should jump right in.
Right in the water.
I'm so happy
I haven't gotten any mosquito bites.
There's no sun either.
(Jungle life is going pretty well.)
Do you want to try sitting here?
Climbing this tree?
- A swing?
- That looks like a swing.
A swing?
(The tree branch is hanging down
like a swing.)
It's like a swing.
How did the tree grow like this?
A natural swing.
Won Ji.
- Won Ji.
- Grab that.
Wait.
It's getting interesting again.
No, I'll sit like a deity.
Like the queen of this jungle.
Okay!
(Shutting her eyes tightly)
Wait.
- Wait.
(Even Ipu realizes she's a scaredy-cat.)
Harimu, try it.
(Gasping)
What did you just do?
What's with me?
(Curled up)
Have fun, girl!
I look like...
I'm pooping.
- Okay!
(Won Ji's turn)
Lift your feet. There you go!
Her belly is shaking.
Won Ji, engage your core.
(Who made her shake?)
That's good.
(Ipu shows off an advanced skill.)
- I want to try that too.
- Try it!
- I want to try that.
- Show me what you've got!
Make it, make it hot!
Show me what you've got!
(It's Gabee's turn.)
This might be really hard.
- Put your leg up there.
- Here?
I'll push it.
(Hanging)
You're doing well! There you go!
You're the best!
(Screaming)
We're in the jungle!
(Showing all her pearly whites)
(Gabee, way to go!)
This is fun.
- It's fun.
- It's so much fun.
- It's really fun.
- Thank you.
There are some activities here and there.
Now let's find some orangutans.
- Okay.
Let's focus and find the orangutans now.
- Orangutans.
- Let's find the orangutans.
There's plenty of fun stuff to do...
besides looking for orangutans.
His "What's in My Room" is so much fun.
- "What's in My Room."
- He has so much fun stuff in his room.
Ipu's house tour.
His house tour is so much fun.
(Deeper into the rainforest)
It's refreshing.
The shade.
(Stepping over a fallen tree)
(Dodging all the vines
as they go deeper into the jungle)
It's getting rougher and rougher.
This is nothing like a regular hike.
We keep having...
- to step over trees.
- Right.
This feels like a real jungle.
This is great.
Look.
He's showing us something new.
- Ipu's not even out of breath.
- A room tour.
Ipu is a walking encyclopedia.
(Orangutan call)
(Surprised)
- What?
- He found something.
He must've found a monkey.
- What?
Isn't he calling them?
It's an orangutan nest.
Really?
- Where?
- There.
- There?
- There it is.
- That dark thing.
- Where?
It's pretty high up.
I only see the nest, not the orangutan.
(Orangutan call)
(Mimics the call)
Can you see it? You know which one, right?
It's that dark thing.
We'll see one soon.
The monkey builds a nest.
So cute.
I can't wait to see an orangutan.
Cute little orangutan.
Will Mr. Orangutan stay up in the trees?
They're mostly in the trees,
but they come down too.
We should watch the trees closely.
I'll look up as we walk now.
So smart.
Brainy, so brainy. Really brainy.
A brainy orangutan.
(Deeper into the mountain forest)
(Orangutan call)
(Repeated orangutan calls)
(Sian slips in an impersonation.)
- Nice.
- That sounded like an orangutan.
You're good at impressions.
(Confident, she makes more ape calls.)
- It's not easy.
- What do you mean, maybe not?
(Maybe not)
- He must've found something else.
- Why are we stopping?
(Ipu suddenly stops.)
I saw a mother orangutan and her baby.
(Are they finally meeting an orangutan?)
(Really?)
He is serious.
(Determined)
Let's follow Ipu.
It's completely muddy.
It's getting more like a jungle.
(Looking around)
(There's an orangutan somewhere nearby.)
Our Tarzan has stopped.
My gosh.
(Shushing)
(Startled)
There's an orangutan nearby.
(Is it nearby?)
(Over there)
(They quietly begin the pursuit.)
I think I hear something.
Slowly.
(Carefully, one step at a time)
That's the person we saw earlier.
(Startled)
I'm sorry.
Hello.
(So happy to see the safety officer
from the entrance)
(I can't with you.)
He told us to be quiet.
We're being quiet now.
Sorry.
I'm bad at reading the room.
I feel like they'll be with us
until tomorrow.
I saw him behind us,
but he keeps appearing ahead.
It's wild. We keep running into him.
(They resume their trek.)
(Ipu suddenly seems to be in a hurry.)
There must be one.
No way.
It's there.
No, it's there. Over there.
It's right there.
(A glimpse of brown)
Where?
- We can go.
- He says to go.
(Beckoning them over)
Let's go.
They're easier to see than I expected.
(Slowly moving higher)
We're really close now.
Here.
Where?
- Here.
- Is it there?
(Thick fur visible through the trees)
There it is.
Amazing!
This is incredible.
- This is amazing.
- Totally.
Let's go.
(They decide to move closer.)
There are two of them.
- Two?
- There are two.
They're so cute.
Are they mother and baby?
(At last, their first orangutan encounter)
- A baby.
A baby and its mother.
A mother and baby.
So cute.
(A baby orangutan with its mother)
- So cute.
- Hello.
(Flailing)
(Dangling)
- Hey there.
- Hi!
Its messy hair is just my style.
So cute.
This is incredible. I never thought
we'd see one this close.
(Its charmingly messy hair)
Hello.
So cute.
It seems to be saying hello to me.
It's peeing.
(Trickling)
It seems to be saying hello.
Hello.
(Peeing instead of saying hello)
There's a baby too.
(A fascinating sight)
Where did the big one go?
It climbed higher.
It's avoiding us.
I think it avoids us because we're human.
This is fascinating.
(Scratching)
It's scratching.
Scratch, scratch.
Its hands are really big.
Its hands are huge.
I can't take my eyes off it.
It pooped.
Poop?
The baby pooped.
Again. Look.
(Plopping)
- Its poop is green.
- You're right.
Is that pee?
Or maybe it's dropping fruit.
Fruit.
(Dropping food as it eats)
Fascinating.
Hello.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I'm from Korea.
It's looking down.
We're fascinated by each other.
This is fascinating.
Should we take a photo together?
- It's close.
- Can you see it?
- It's here.
- Is it here?
I think it's there. Or is that not it?
I think that's it.
(The orangutan in the middle)
Hello.
- This is amazing.
- We even watched them eat.
The difference in size is enormous.
- Exactly.
- The mom is huge, but the baby is tiny.
This is fascinating.
It's amazing how he walks barefoot.
(Carefully following Ipu)
There are monkeys.
- Monkeys?
- Yes.
Another monkey?
It's over there!
That's a baby.
A monkey is here?
(Peeking out)
There's a monkey?
- So cute.
- It's close.
It's passing in front of us.
(A pig-tailed macaque)
It's not the same kind as earlier.
It's just a baby.
So freaking cute.
We're seeing many moms and babies today.
And what's so cute is...
- it touches the tree before going.
- Before crossing?
- Like testing a bridge?
- Look before you leap.
Shake a tree before climbing it.
So cute.
- My goodness.
- So cute.
(An adorable baby monkey)
It eats things off the tree.
I can't handle how cute it is.
I can't handle this.
It's so cute.
It looks just like a person.
Its ears and ribs too.
Our guide Ipu...
(Monkey call)
is great at spotting monkeys.
(Imitating the call)
(Monkey call)
But Ipu is amazing.
How does he know this path?
- Right.
- He knows it by heart?
He memorized every path.
That's so impressive.
He must come here all the time, right?
(Did Ipu find something else?)
What is it?
Why are you standing so solemnly, Ipu?
You startled me.
What is it?
There must be something.
What is it this time?
That scared me.
(Could something be wrong?)
(Watching him carefully)
You can eat fruit here.
It must be time to eat fruit.
(That's it?)
But he sounded so serious saying it.
That was scary.
I thought there was a tiger.
(The impersonation begins.)
Eat fruit.
It's very hot.
- "It's very hot, so come over here?"
- It's very hot?
This is so funny.
I'm losing it.
"Very hot."
Ipu is my type of guy.
Which one of Ipu's rooms is this?
- The 20th.
- The 20th?
- He keeps searching for things.
- Exactly.
How can he even see that?
Just seeing this is incredible.
And he keeps making this face.
You're good at that.
(Serious)
That's good.
Eat fruit.
(Ipu has a character.)
- This is so funny.
- He's different when looking at us...
compared to when he's looking
for an orangutan.
He goes like this.
He's good at his job.
I have some fruit for you.
(Finally, it's break time!)
What kind of fruit?
I have some bananas, oranges,
passion fruit,
pineapple,
and dragon fruit.
Dragon fruit!
That's quite a variety.
He's even setting up seats for us
with the banana leaf.
The banana leaf...
(Eco-friendly sitting mat)
I don't think that's our seat.
It's probably going to be our dish.
Oh, a dish.
A fruit dish.
That's how it was when I looked it up.
- See? Research is important.
- I've seen it.
- It's usually for the plate.
- I see.
We almost sat on it.
(Fruit dish almost became butt dish.)
(Rustle)
I see a monkey!
Maybe he smelled the fruit.
There he is.
- Where do you see them?
- Over there.
I see him.
He has gray fur.
I see another species.
He looks like he's wearing a mask.
He's leaning his head on the tree.
He's so cute.
He looks like a penguin.
(Spotted a surprisingly stylish monkey)
He kind of looks like he's wearing
a Muay Thai mask.
He reminds me of "King of Masked Singer."
(Chuckle)
He kind of does.
He can definitely enter
"King of Masked Singer."
(Thomas's langur: endemic
to northern Sumatra,)
(known for mask-like facial markings.)
His tail is super long.
Right.
He has a long tail.
His tail is longer than his body.
He looks so mysterious.
He's beautiful.
How do you say "long tail" in Korean?
"Gin kkori."
"Gin kkori wonsungi."
Your pronunciation is very good.
Ipu's pronunciation is so good.
(He can traverse the jungle
with a tail longer than his body.)
Come this way.
Ipu's telling us to come.
- Let's go.
- He's so cute.
Oh my god!
He's right in front of us.
How cute.
- He seems shy.
- His tail is super long.
The way he's perched is so cute.
(Saying hello up close.)
His head is so small.
Doesn't he remind you of Sun Wukong?
He looks like a character
from "Romance of the Three Kingdoms."
I think it's his hair.
He has an edgy hairstyle.
He kind of does.
I like it.
His hairstyle is cool.
- He must groom himself well.
- He has a mohawk hairstyle.
He's very cool. So funky.
Let's go back.
I think our fruit is almost ready.
Let's go.
That was so cute.
Right, he was so cute.
Oh, we meet again.
Won Ji, he's here again.
- He's Won Ji's favorite.
- Just a second.
I'm going to interview him.
How are you?
What's your name?
(Puzzled)
John.
- Are you from Indonesia?
- Yes.
Are you part of our team?
Yeah, I'm the park security here.
We met three times, remember?
Yeah.
- So that's why he was everywhere.
- He was the security.
- You're the security.
- The security.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Finally, the mystery solves itself.
I thought he was part of our team.
(The fruits are still being prepared.)
(Rustle)
Look, look!
- The monkey came.
- They must be here for the fruit.
- Do you think it's the same one?
- Let's invite them over.
Oh, it's peeing.
It would be so funny if it peed here.
Is it the same monkey from before?
It must have smelled the fruit.
It's practically drooling already.
Hey, don't poop here, okay?
There are some monkeys above us too.
There are so many.
They must have smelled our fruit.
It's super crowded up there.
They must be waiting until we leave.
They're waiting for our leftovers.
"Slurp."
Look over there!
Where?
We're surrounded.
There's one there...
and another over there.
- Look over there.
- We're surrounded.
I think I see a baby monkey.
There's a baby over there.
How young do you think it is?
Looks very young.
It's right next to her.
Look at the baby.
(Fluffy baby monkey)
- So small.
- They're so cute.
Super cute.
How adorable.
Such a baby, right?
Could it be a newborn?
I see one over there, too.
(Amazed)
So cute.
The baby monkey...
is so cute.
(Amazed and excited)
There's one over there, too.
This is so amazing.
(Slipping back to mom's arms)
Now, let's eat the fruit.
Wow.
This is so pretty.
The watermelon's so red.
The colors are beautiful.
Look at the watermelon.
I see mandarin oranges, too.
(Colors blended by nature)
It's so pretty.
Look, he sandwiched passionfruit
between pineapple slices.
True foodie.
(He knows what he's doing
as a legendary foodie.)
"True foodie."
A culinary genius.
This is so refreshing.
We have oranges and bananas.
How pretty.
They took such care.
(Decorated with flowers.)
The colors are arranged so beautifully.
So pretty.
(Almost too pretty to eat)
You can eat now.
- Thank you!
- Thank you for the fruit.
Watermelons are my favorite.
(Chomp)
This is so sweet.
Getting my daily dose of vitamins!
It's incredibly sweet.
The pineapple-passionfruit sandwich
is so good.
Pineapples are so tangy.
It's good, right?
- It's very refreshing.
- He's indeed a foodie expert.
(Getting proper vitamins)
(Some fruit for Ipu
after all his hard work.)
Ipu,
can I have one mandarin orange?
Just one.
He gave me two.
Do you want some?
(Resorts to stealing fruit
because it's so good.)
The mandarin orange is so delicious.
I feel recharged.
Do you want to try this one, too?
I want to try.
Thank you.
What is it?
That's snake fruit.
(Salak: a tropical fruit
often called snakefruit...)
(due to its scaly skin.)
How do we eat this? Do we just peel it?
Oh, you just peel it.
(White flesh exposed when peeled off)
Like garlic?
(Chomp after making it bite-sized)
Okay.
- Do we put the peels here?
- Yeah.
Okay.
It's delicious.
Do you want to try?
It smells nice.
It's tangy.
(Nom)
It tastes like chestnuts but sour.
Do you not like it? I like its aroma.
You have to take out the seed.
(Chomp)
The fruit inside is delicious.
Can this cause diarrhea?
No, no.
It prevents diarrhea.
So it's the opposite.
When you have a stomachache,
eating this would stop it?
So it works like anti-diarrhea medicine.
Right.
I think it's a good idea to eat this.
We would be in trouble if we need
to go number 2 in the jungle.
Do you want to see a magic trick?
(Bring it already.)
He's going to show us a magic trick.
Is there anything he can't do?
What if all the monkeys gather around?
Wow.
It's magic plastic.
He's really good.
Ipu the piper.
Wow.
(Ipu can do anything.)
Do you want to see another trick?
Second magic trick?
(Open)
Where did he come from?
(It's a snake!)
It's a real snake.
(Shocked)
Wow.
(Snake engaging with his core)
(Flicking his tongue.)
Is it okay to do that?
(Folding him neatly)
(Ah)
No, don't do that.
Is it even safe?
(He put the snake in his mouth.)
Is he really doing this?
(Do not attempt.)
(This was filmed safely
with a trained professional.)
(Shocked)
That's crazy.
Wow, I can't believe it.
Amazing.
(A jaw-dropping stunt)
(Snake coming out of the mouth)
Wow.
Did he eat the snake?
Wait.
It's like kissing.
Oh my gosh.
I guess that snake isn't venomous.
He could give Mr. Kim Byung-man
a run for his money.
Right.
The snake looks so harmless.
It's kind of cute.
What a derpy little noodle.
The way it's hissing reminds me
of a chihuahua barking.
He's so small.
Come on.
Can I touch it?
(Slip)
I want to touch it too.
Don't tease me, okay?
- "Don't tease me."
- Good snake.
(Tremble)
She's always so scared,
but she still wants to touch.
(She's a brave scaredy cat.)
Curiosity got the best of me.
(Trying again)
She got up the courage.
(Frowning)
(Jump)
(Teasing the scaredy cat for fun)
So cute.
- It's slippery. Touch it.
- Oh gosh!
Slippery.
(Too fun not to do it again.)
Okay, let's get back to the jungle.
Okay, back to the jungle.
- Are you leaving?
- Goodbye!
(Thanks for bearing with us.)
This is so much fun.
So fun.
They keep coming down.
There's one more.
- I think they want to eat the fruit.
- Yeah.
Are we allowed to feed them?
- No.
- Okay.
It's just for people?
Yes, for people only.
Not for animals.
(Feeding wildlife is strictly prohibited
to protect the ecosystem.)
After we're done,
let's go to our campsite.
It takes another two hours.
- Two hours?
- You can finish the fruit first.
Uphills and downhills.
- After we finish eating?
- Yes.
We've charged our energy!
He says the uphills and downhills
come after this.
- So eat up.
- Got it.
Okay. Let's go to camp
after we finish this.
Okay.
Follow Ipu.
We follow Ipu.
Let's go together.
(Indonesia)
(They'll be traveling
for another two hours.)
(Back on the trail with music)
- Abra-ca-Empty
(Can't have a jungle without this song!)
- Let it all go
- Get rid of it
Get rid of it all!
We really got rid of it all today.
- We really did.
- True.
This song's a bop.
This is where the real trek begins.
The vines have turned into stairs.
Vine stairs.
Talk about hitting the vine jackpot.
Forget deep roots.
We've got the whole vine now.
We've come down a long way.
Right?
You can see some houses down there.
It's a village.
Ipu.
Is that our camp?
Not now.
Two more hours to go.
- Two hours?
- Another two hours?
- He says it's not here.
Two hours of uphill and downhill.
So it starts now.
I guess we have to go up once.
- Up and down.
- He says it keeps coming.
Up, down, up, up, down
(Singing their worries away)
She's so funny.
My kind of humor.
I can hear something refreshing.
Huh?
What?
We're crossing over water?
I don't see any way around the water.
Ipu!
- Do we have to go there?
- Yeah.
Seriously?
(A wild stream appears.)
So this is why Ipu came barefoot.
Do we have to take our shoes off?
I think we're just going to get wet.
We keep them on.
I guess it's better than going barefoot.
Be careful.
Wow, it's really steep.
Careful, it's slippery.
- Be careful, everyone!
- Okay.
(Carefully)
(Slippery)
Watch your steps.
Please keep a safe distance.
(Wet ground means
keeping your distance is a must.)
It's like a refreshing little waterfall.
It looks so refreshing!
Wow, it really feels refreshing.
- It's so different.
- I want to dip my feet in so bad.
I'm going to wash my hands and my face.
Wow, so cold!
This feels so good.
(Feels like the heat just melted away)
Should I try dipping my feet in?
Let's do it.
Shall we?
(Rolling up the pants)
I think it'd be less slippery
with shoes on.
Wow, it's so cold.
- Did you just walk in?
- Yeah!
It's so refreshing. I want to stay here.
- Seriously.
- Really?
I want to lie down here.
Me too.
Just letting go
and getting my shoes soaked...
feels so damn good.
I want to jump in.
The water in my shoes...
feels so weird.
But I don't want to leave.
Because leaving this place
is probably going to feel worse.
I'm feeling exactly that right now.
It feels pretty bad.
But we're probably going to get
wet again, right?
- Of course.
- Up and down.
Just when our shoes start to dry,
it's downhill again.
Alright.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go!
(After a brief break, they keep going.)
Shoes are a little slippery
now that they're wet.
Be careful.
It's pretty steep.
Ugh.
Darn.
Gosh.
Wait, is it all uphill from here?
Up down.
- Everyone okay?
- I'm okay.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
(Already two hours into the jungle trek)
(Even Miss Sunshine is out of smiles.)
Just a moment.
We must be at least halfway there, right?
Two more hours of up and down.
Two more hours?
- Why isn't the time reduced?
- Can we just sleep here?
How's there still that much time left?
An hour ago,
you said it'll take two hours.
And now, you're telling us
there are two more hours.
To make you happy.
(Pause)
Why do you keep saying...
there are two hours left?
I want to make you feel happy.
- I'm not happy.
- "Two hours left."
It's not even 40 minutes or something.
But 2 hours feels so far away.
There's only so much false hope
we can take.
This isn't false hope. It's just torture!
Can you smell it?
He's really good at distracting us.
Do you see that mountain?
Two more hours of up and down
until we reach there.
- That mountain?
- Yeah.
Two more hours of up and down.
I don't like that.
- Why?
Who could do it?
- You.
- Me?
Let me see.
Can you sleep in the jungle?
"Let me see."
"Let me see," she says.
Let's go with orangutans.
Okay, with orangutans!
With orangutans!
With orangutans,
we can do everything!
- With orangutans!
- Yeah, let's go!
I love the energy.
This is crazy.
(After all that uphill...)
(Now it's endless downhill.)
(30 minutes into the downhill course)
- Are you okay?
- Yes!
- It's okay. I'm okay.
- Is number 1 okay?
Number 1 is not okay.
- Is number 2 okay?
- Number 3, no.
Number 2 is okay!
Alright, even numbers!
Odd and even!
Odd numbers are not okay,
even numbers are okay.
I can call for a helicopter later.
- Huh?
- A helicopter.
An elephant?
Helicopter!
- Helicopter.
- An elephant?
Helicopter!
Chuff!
She's gone mad.
The heat's gotten into her.
Good lord.
She's gone crazy!
(Random bursts of high energy)
Ipu.
- Are you tired?
- No.
- But you look tired.
- You look tired.
- I saw that.
(You definitely sighed just now.)
- Tired.
- You?
- You.
- Not me.
Not me, he says.
Okay.
Let me see.
Ipu.
Does the campsite...
have snakes there?
- Snakes at the campsite?
- Yes, snakes.
Only crocodiles.
Only crocodiles?
Crocodiles?
What about tigers?
Tigers are already gone.
Already gone? Where to?
Where did they go?
(Ipu picks something up
instead of answering.)
Ipu, what's that?
Fruit.
- Fruit?
- Yes.
That's what gets me. So funny.
He can't be bothered to answer.
He's tired.
- Are you tired?
- No.
No?
What fruit is it?
(Endless questions)
He danced instead of answering me.
- He seems tired.
- Very.
We have two hours left.
You've got this, right?
You've got this.
He's so funny.
There's water.
Wow, a creek!
Our shower place!
(A river appears beyond the dense jungle.)
(The current looks pretty strong.)
You can swim here.
- What did you say?
- What?
We're crossing the river?
- Yes.
- Wow, okay.
We just jump in there?
The current's pretty strong here.
Liar!
You're a liar.
(They have to wade across
to the other side.)
(Unexpected underwater trekking)
How are we going to cross over
with all our stuff?
It looks pretty deep.
I think it comes up to your thighs.
Still, what do we do?
(For safety, the crew crosses first.)
They're linking arms
so they don't get swept away.
(Watching makes them even more nervous.)
Our buddies crossing the river.
I'm gonna get soaked anyway,
so I might as well roll it down.
He says it's going to be
slippery barefoot.
I'll be fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'll try.
Okay.
We'll be grabbing this.
Okay, let's go!
(Won Ji carefully takes her first step.)
- It's cold.
- It's refreshing.
Ipu, you're too fast.
Ipu is too fast.
The current is really strong,
so we have to walk diagonally.
The current is really strong.
It doesn't look like it, though.
(She staggers if she lets her guard down.)
(The younger ones
slowly enter the water too.)
(Harimu is the only one taking it easy.)
It's slippery.
The current is really strong.
The current is insane.
(Especially hard for a paper doll,
who lacks balance)
I can't keep my balance.
(She bravely pushes
through the strong current.)
This is fun.
(The eldest gains
confidence and speeds up.)
(Gabee and Harimu slow down
for the frightened Sian.)
She's already way over there.
I made it. Thank you, Ipu.
It's so cool.
This is so refreshing.
(The younger ones are almost there too.)
(They safely crossed the river.)
We're eating here.
- Let's go eat.
- I'm exhausted.
- Harimu, do you want to get in the water?
- Yes.
Should we just soak our feet?
I wanna take this off and get in.
(Staggering)
This is like dancing too.
(She turns her fall into a scorpion pose.)
I'm dying.
It's so refreshing.
- I just want to stay here.
- Me too.
It's so cool.
(Looking around)
Ipu, what are you looking for?
A stone.
Another new thing.
He's doing something fun again.
I think this is mud.
(Ipu shows off a new trick.)
It really rubs off on his hand.
(A clay-like stone that turns into mud)
That's amazing.
It's totally like a crayon.
What is this?
A stone.
A stone?
(It is a stone, though.)
- A stone?
- Yes.
The color is so vivid.
(Smoothing)
(Ipu paints Gabee's face.)
(He starts decorating Gabee.)
(With careful touches)
Looks like he's just playing around.
(Laughing)
I think it's done.
(He even pays attention to the symmetry.)
Ipu did this for me.
(Like a fierce cat)
(The artist proudly admires his work.)
(Glancing)
Come here, Ipu.
I can write your name in Korean.
Do you want to see?
(Deeply focused)
(She carefully writes his name.)
- This is your name.
- Thank you.
Done. I like it.
I wrote his name on his arm.
That's so sweet.
(It's pretty, so it's fine.)
This might work.
Let's try writing Abra-ca-Empty with it.
"Empty."
(Swiping)
(She leaves a semi-permanent memory.)
This is our mark.
You've decorated diaries before, right?
Of course I have.
Hello.
Here's your lunch.
(Lunch is finally ready.)
- What's that?
- This looks so nice.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(Lunch is nasi goreng
topped with chicken.)
This is amazing.
Chicken.
(Pretty much means "thank you so much.")
Eating with our feet
in the water would be amazing.
I'd be so happy.
Should I sit here?
(She finds a suitable rock and sits.)
(They take a bite
as soon as they sit down.)
It's spicy and so good.
Is this nasi goreng?
Yes, I think so.
(Now, a bite of chicken)
The chicken is good.
Exactly.
(Excited)
I love this.
Beer.
(The vibe makes you crave a beer.)
A bottle of beer.
There's nothing Ipu can't do.
He's using a piece of plastic.
(Making bird sounds
with a piece of plastic)
The sound is cute.
(He plays birdsong
using a piece of plastic.)
(They savor the chicken,
listening to artificial bird sounds.)
It's so delicious.
(Ipu wanders off somewhere again.)
Look at Ipu's nails.
He puts fake nails on his fingers.
- Oh, right.
- Look at that.
Is that real?
(He returns with nail extensions.)
- It's crazy.
- Ipu is a local here.
Harimu, bring it on.
- Harimu, bring it on.
- Why are they so long?
I'm seriously jealous.
(Ipu's nails become communal property.)
It's stealing our food.
Hey.
(The monkey eats and runs.)
It eats behind us.
(It snatches their food in an instant.)
It's cute.
- Amazing.
- It's eating in such a hurry.
They're having the time of their lives.
(Almost like a company dinner)
Monkey.
What are you doing? Come here.
(A quick monkey playtime)
(She plays well.)
Hold on.
Look over there.
(A new creature appears.)
A lizard?
- There really is a crocodile.
- It's huge.
It's not a crocodile, is it?
It's a lizard.
Its tongue is completely black.
I'm a huge fan of those.
It's eyeing Ipu's bag.
(It shows interest in Ipu's bag.)
No, stop.
Ipu's eyes have changed again.
(The bag owner's gaze
suddenly turns fierce.)
Is he hunting?
This is true nature.
(A standoff over the bag)
Amazing.
(Sneaking closer)
(Threatening)
(Flinches)
They're exactly alike.
I think Ipu's trying to catch it.
This is an incredibly tense standoff.
Between Ipu...
(Thrilling)
And the lizard.
(He approaches at its eye level.)
I think he's going to catch it.
(Dashing)
(The water monitor briefly retreats.)
(He chases it fiercely.)
(Is it retreating for good?)
(Swishes around)
(Chaos)
(It charges straight
at the two biggest scaredy-cats.)
(It makes a beeline for the river.)
It's amazing.
It's insane.
(An undignified exit)
It's funny how it
suddenly started swimming.
Pure nature.
I'd get to see a real lizard
in the wild for the first time.
It'd be so scary if they came out
while we're sleeping.
- Oh, no.
- They might come out at night.
I should hug my bag while I sleep.
I won't be able to sleep tonight.
Okay.
We're heading to the campsite now.
- Okay.
- Finally.
It takes two hours.
- Don't lie.
(The cry-wolf uncle
keeps going without a care.)
Okay, let's go.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's see.
Let's see if it really takes two hours.
So far, we've been in the mountains.
Now it's starting to feel like a jungle.
There are so many more weeds.
It's getting more and more jungle-like.
It really feels like a jungle.
There seem to be lots of plants
you'd find in a jungle.
Right.
It looks like nature is
really well preserved here.
- I love it.
- I love it too.
It's much denser,
and the path has gotten really narrow.
I feel like I've come to a new planet.
It's awesome.
(Deeper and deeper into the jungle)
What are we doing
when we get to the campsite?
- Ipu.
- Yes.
Do we have a schedule?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Nothing today.
(Yay, free time)
Nice. Let's swim and play.
We definitely have to swim here.
(He spots something.)
What's that?
Is that the nail?
(Those nails from the stream)
Harimu, are you nervous?
- No.
- Are you?
No.
They look like they're
five times longer than your nails.
I know.
Isn't he making them too long?
I've never seen anyone
with longer nails than yours.
Natural nails.
(A slight sense of danger)
He's making them way too long.
(Challenge)
(How dare you.)
(Staggering)
(Queen Ipu's legs give out.)
Sorry.
- Oh, my.
- He's so charming.
Ipu is so charming.
(Ipu is acting cute.)
You're so funny.
You're very funny.
But it's so fun that everything here is...
basically his toy and his playground.
Exactly. That's so Ipu.
There's an even more
amazing spot over there.
There's someone over there too.
We're not crossing over there, are we?
Is that our campsite?
Yes, that's it.
- Over there.
- Really?
(The campsite is across the stream.)
(Their second crossing already)
We're going.
It's refreshing.
This looks like it'll be the deepest one.
It's deep.
The current is really strong.
It's nice.
It's a funny life.
It's a very good life.
It's refreshing.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm so all right.
- Nice.
- It's refreshing.
(The cool water washes away all the heat.)
Thank you.
Thank you, Ipu.
(Ipu, thanks.)
(They finally crossed the river.)
It's so nice.
They're swimming over there.
Let's swim later too.
Here?
Is that our campsite?
You said we had two more hours to go.
You're a liar.
- Two minutes.
- Yes!
- Finally, only two minutes.
- Jungle!
- Welcome to the Jungle.
(As soon as we walk in,
they see an old, rundown hut.)
No way. Wait.
Hold on.
- I can't believe it.
- Those are bamboo houses.
Please. This is a lie.
(Flustered)
(Staggering)
How do people even find a place like this?
Seriously, this is legendary.
(Today's lodging is Eco-friendly.)
(About a four-hour trek to get here)
This is pretty much
an indigenous experience.
I should've brought just one outfit.
(It took them eight hours
to get here from Medan.)
It's just divided into different spaces.
It's really well built with bamboo.
It's totally a bamboo house.
What is that?
(Orangutans show up here all the time.)
(This jungle lodge coexists
with the wildlife.)
There are so many houses here.
Where's our home?
- The blue one.
That must be it.
Let's go.
Let's check it out.
This is it.
This is your room.
(Arriving at their lodging
eight hours after leaving their hotel)
A room tour.
What?
That's unbelievable.
- How can it be like this?
- Gosh.
I've never slept in a place like this.
How is this possible?
(Here's today's lodging.)
(You can see the entire interior
at a glance.)
(An ultra-minimalist lodge)
There's our backpack!
Our backpack is here.
This is insane.
Let us take a look around our room.
A room tour.
Room One.
Room Two.
Room Three.
Room Four.
And...
there are no windows.
(This room feels insanely open.)
The mosquito net has a hole in it.
(Stunned)
- Do you like it?
- It's good!
- Thank you.
There's no electricity.
- No electricity?
- No.
- No lights either?
- Yes.
Okay.
- You're right.
- There's nothing here.
You don't get a signal here either.
We should rely on our video light.
If you want to make a call,
climb up a tree.
Okay.
If we get bored, let's climb a tree.
(Losing her mind)
This is so romantic.
Oh, my. This is nice.
Yes.
(Laughing)
I wish nighttime would never come
and it could just stay like this all day.
- Wouldn't it be scary at night?
- I think so too.
We might hear a lot of animals at night.
There are no doors. It's all open.
Monkeys can come in and take something
while we're sleeping.
We should be careful.
(Orangutans also pop up
from time to time.)
(They roam freely through the trees...)
(and all around the area.)
(Take good care of your backpack.)
- How about snakes?
- Even if you see them, that's fine.
Just put them in your mouths.
Is that everything?
- It's here.
- Where?
This is everything.
- All we have is one backpack.
- One bag.
We're compact.
One bag for four people.
You have one bag for yourself.
- Why?
I don't know.
Ask him.
Hello.
Why do they share one bag?
(Satisfying)
- Excuse me.
- Why?
Even Ipu is asking why.
He finds it strange too.
Even though he feels at home in nature.
Not enough.
Right. It's not enough.
Even the nature man has one bag.
(They're more minimalist
than someone living in nature.)
I'm so sweaty, I want to get in the water.
Let's go for a swim.
Let's shower there.
- Okay.
- Really?
- Let's go.
- Sounds good.
- Right away.
- Go now.
What did you say?
- "Go now."
We're just saying, "Let's go."
- Let's go. Go now.
- Go now.
(He learned quickly.)
Go now
(Today's shower spot is the river
they just crossed.)
- Gosh!
- We're here.
Let's go in.
The water looks blue.
Let's take our shoes off and jump in!
Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Bamboo!
What is that? I want to ride on that.
What is that?
- Awesome.
- That's cool.
It's refreshing.
I'm going in.
(Getting ready to get in the water)
(Running into the water)
Wait. I'm drifting away.
(A cold shower)
- I'm drifting away.
- It's carrying me away.
- Goodbye!
We're throwing off all the shackles
of the world,
and heading back to Korea.
There's a monkey over there.
Where?
It stopped.
(There are monkeys everywhere you look.)
Your butt.
Your butt looks huge.
(Her butt is filled with air.)
You're farting.
(Splashing around
with just their faces above the surface)
Harimu is here.
Harimu, come on in.
- I'm back.
- Come on.
(Playing and showering at the same time)
Her waacking is crazy.
(Twerking)
(A new skill, twerking in the water!)
(Twerking for the members again)
(Satisfied)
That's so funny.
Is it okay to wash your hair
with just water?
I think so.
It's super cold.
It's waking me up. My brain!
I can feel my brain.
- It's so cold.
- I can feel my brain.
- I can really feel my brain.
- Let me wash your hair.
- My brain feels alive.
- Let me massage your head.
It's so refreshing.
Ma'am.
Let me give you a head massage.
- A head massage for you too.
- Thank you.
(The water is nice, and Sian is kind.)
I feel so free.
- This is paradise.
- Really.
Then you get up and see nature.
You can see nature in every direction.
- Nature on the side too.
- The view is stunning.
The perfect view for a mountain spirit.
Aren't we like fairies now?
I'll wash this too.
Woodcutter! Don't steal my clothes.
- You're watching us!
- Woodcutter!
Don't steal my clothes.
- You're so mean.
- Okay?
- Even if you like me, don't steal it.
- Don't steal it.
What's the purpose of this swimming?
Don't steal it.
We've become nature people.
(Scooping)
It's really refreshing.
Harimu washes her face
in an interesting way.
(The queen doesn't lower her head
to wash her face.)
(Standing)
- It's so nice.
- It's refreshing.
I feel like I'm at an outdoor hot spring.
A cold spring.
A cold spring?
- It looks good. What is it?
- I don't know what it is.
Let's sit down and eat.
Okay.
Hey!
- Hey!
- It stole our food.
Hey!
Hey, that's mine!
- Gosh.
- That was mine!
- Give it back!
- What did it take?
Our food.
It wasn't scared at all.
(Collecting)
They just eat everything.
- They're not picky.
- We have one more.
- What is this?
- Fried sweet potato?
(Trying the snack later than the monkey)
Let me pour it.
- It reminds me of makgeolli.
- Right.
- A cup of tea?
- It's coffee.
A warm coffee.
You need hot coffee at a time like this.
I usually prefer iced coffee,
but I want hot coffee now.
Wait. We have sugar here.
You can add it if you want.
- If you like coffee, add some.
- Yes.
- Cheers.
(Slurping)
It's good.
Wow.
I think this coffee's
naturally a little sweet.
Yeah. I love it.
- It's a bit toasty.
- It tastes just like scorched rice.
It's so good.
What's this?
Shall we try this?
Fried bananas?
(Trying it immediately.)
Fried sweet potatoes!
Fried sweet pumpkins!
- Sweet pumpkins?
- Sweet potatoes!
It's so good.
It tastes like fries.
Wow!
- It's good, right?
- So crunchy.
It's sweet and savory.
They seasoned it.
Mmm!
It's so good.
Yeah.
I can see why the monkeys took it.
Something even monkeys want.
- They took a lot.
- Like four.
Four or six, I think.
- So greedy.
- They took a lot.
(A warm treat even the monkeys
can't resist.)
We have nothing to do now.
Our phones have no connection.
When it gets dark,
we won't even have that.
- Lamps.
- No lights.
- What do we do now?
- Oh, no.
We really have nothing to do.
(Staring)
You guys totally look like a hiking club.
This would be perfect for a dating show.
No. 1, 2, 3, 4.
Then...
We've got nothing else to do.
So let's film a dating show.
We've got five ladies and five gents here.
Damn.
Let's be honest. Is there anyone here...
getting a little boost from anyone?
Is anyone making this journey
a little easier?
(And no one found their motivation.)
Hands up!
Nothing gives me a dopamine rush
like romance.
- A show within a show.
- Yeah.
(An evening in the jungle
with no electricity or dopamine.)
As soon as we get down tomorrow,
I'm heading straight to the laundromat.
(Hanging wet clothes.)
Are you heading to that table?
Are you getting closer?
Are you sitting there?
Are you going for her?
(Squeezing dopamine)
(Happy)
(They chat away until sunset.)
(Meanwhile, Ipu is preparing
something for them.)
(Handmade from jungle wood)
(Crackle)
Ooh, a campfire.
Now that's a fire!
(Ipu's cozy campfire)
Wow, that fire's really roaring.
You can hear it roaring.
- This feels nice.
- So nice.
I love this vibe.
Campfire show.
(The fire burns bright as night falls.)
What was the highlight of the day
for everyone?
I honestly thought...
I'd be drenched in sweat.
But the weather was surprisingly nice.
- It was a healing course.
- I agree.
(Beautiful weather made the trek
all the more relaxing.)
Ipu was...
such a perfect guide.
Totally.
When Ipu first came to us and said,
"Let's go to the jungle."
That moment.
And the moment he said
we'd be sleeping in there.
- We were like, what?
- What?
(During today's breakfast)
Let me explain a little about the jungle.
Wow!
(We didn't think we'd go to a jungle.)
- That was a terrifying moment.
- Yeah.
Seriously, why are we even here?
After having such a nice breakfast
at the resort this morning.
I know, right? That place was fire.
It's dinner!
(Turning)
(And just in time, dinner is served.)
Dinner time!
It looks so good!
(Can't help but clap.)
It's full Indonesian style.
How did they even cook all this?
Curry!
Wow, these look amazing.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
(The full dinner spread is ready.)
I'm going for curry.
I love curry.
(Won Ji goes for curry first.)
This curry's really thin.
Yeah, it's very soupy.
(Almost like soup)
(Mix it all up.)
(And dig right in.)
(Another bite)
As a curry lover, how's Indonesian curry?
It's not as curry-like.
It's got a hint of curry.
But it's pretty thin
and really heavy on the spices.
It's good.
This looks good too. What is it?
I think it's like braised chicken.
(Nom)
Mmm.
This is so good!
- Is it good?
- Yes.
Are you talking about this one?
Okay.
(Savory chicken, stir-fried with spices.)
Let me try some.
(Nom)
It's like an Indonesian version
of spicy braised chicken.
(You're right.)
I think this is tofu.
(Sian's on a roll,
trying yet another dish.)
It's good!
Tofu.
(Her foodie buddy grabs some right away.)
It's good, isn't it?
(Their tastes are in sync.)
- It's so good.
- A little like gochujang.
It's very Korean.
They all have this underlying flavor.
It's got this hint of...
Sichuan pepper throughout.
I absolutely love it.
(Haha)
I love it too.
Why's Indonesian food so good?
What's this?
Tofu?
(Meanwhile, Harimu tries a new dish.)
No way.
Potato croquette!
(Nom)
- Potato croquette.
- Sounds delicious.
Okay!
(Croquette feast begins.)
It's croquettes and nothing else for her.
(Gabee tries the croquettes too.)
- It's really salty.
- Which one?
- This.
- Yeah.
(Balance out the saltiness
with some shrimp chips.)
(Crunch)
It tastes so good
after being in the water.
Yeah.
It's so good.
(Nom)
(Digging into the jungle buffet.)
Honestly...
I didn't think
we'd get to feast like this.
I think we're all eating better here
than we do outside.
They even gave us snacks.
It's almost like a resort.
An all-inclusive.
The fire makes it smell like
we're out in the country.
(Thunder)
Whoa, thunder and lightning!
- Rumble!
- No way.
I think it's going to rain soon.
Why is there always lightning here?
I know, right?
Let's talk about...
our first impressions of each other.
- I like that.
- Oh, wow.
(There's always one person
who's into this stuff.)
I've known Gabee...
- for about 10 years.
- Oh, really?
- You were her student, right?
- Yes.
Being able to finally...
see her as an older sister on this trip...
means a lot to me.
It feels weird.
She's technically my teacher.
- Ms. Gabee!
- But I wanted us to be like sisters.
That's what I wanted on the first day.
But from day one,
she made me feel really comfortable.
She said, "It might feel awkward,
but just think of me as your big sister."
And I could tell she really meant it.
- You were touched.
- It was so sincere.
Yeah.
That's right. I thought you'd feel
a little uncomfortable.
I was so worried about that.
- Since you two are in the same field.
- Exactly.
- She's kind of senior.
- Of course.
And honestly,
I think the dance scene...
really needs someone like her.
I mean it.
I mean every word.
We need a dance star!
- Dance star.
- I mean it.
- We're going to be dance stars!
- Yes! Okay!
The next dance stars.
I'd seen Gabee...
plenty of times before.
- We met on "World Dice Tour" too.
- Yeah.
She's really thoughtful...
- and always looks out for people.
- So true.
I realized I hadn't been wrong
about her after all.
That's our queen Gabee!
(Laughing)
You really sound like a true fan!
That's our queen!
As for Sian...
At first, I wasn't sure if Sian
and I would really get along.
Oh, why?
Because...
I'd seen her clash with some
of the girls on "Single's Inferno."
(She thought Sian was a total ice queen.)
- Darn!
- But!
She was like, "Gabee!"
Yeah.
Was I like this?
That's the vibe she gave me.
She was totally giving
little sister vibes.
Yeah.
And she's so nice.
(Blushing)
So nice.
And Sian was the last one to arrive.
The last one.
Like the wildcard.
- A wildcard.
- When I saw her...
I was like,
"Who's that gorgeous silhouette?"
Exactly.
So these two were like,
"Is she an actress?"
Really?
Then I recognized you as you got closer.
(Kyaaa!)
I felt like I could really lean on you.
- Right away.
- Really?
So, were you able to?
Yeah, totally!
May seem aloof,
but actually a total softie.
(Sian's actually such a sweetheart.)
I saw you on YouTube.
You're such a strong, determined person.
You made me realize successful people...
- really do have that inner strength.
- I thought that too.
You're so responsible.
- You really come off as a strong woman.
- Yeah.
A cute voice.
But a strong core.
(Strong)
- Meow.
- That's what that is.
When I told people
I was doing a show like this,
they all said,
"I hope Won Ji's on it."
"Please become friends with her!"
"Please!"
And you were actually there.
But you seemed a little...
startled.
- You were a little taken aback.
- Yeah.
- "Oh..."
- "What kind of combination is this?"
Yeah.
I could feel her.
A little surprised.
So I decided to approach her slowly.
See? She's really quick
at figuring people out.
That's what I thought.
But I feel like we really click.
I could totally brag about it
to my friends.
"We're basically besties now!"
- Jealous?
- Besties!
I think I could brag like this
when I go back.
You're so much fun.
I had only seen Harimu through Reels.
I'm honored.
I honestly thought she was a foreigner.
That's the best compliment.
- I thought you were a foreigner.
- That can happen.
I only knew Harimu...
from a distance.
We never really had time to get close
or get to know her personality.
But it turns out she is
such a great person.
It made me wonder why I
never took the time to get to know her.
I wish I had.
That really is a compliment.
It's not like I had a bad impression
of you before, but...
I don't really...
- Show your personality, right?
- Exactly.
I noticed.
I like getting to know someone
naturally over time.
I like meeting people naturally.
I strongly prefer
meeting people naturally.
(That's why she kept insisting
on "meeting naturally.")
She seemed like a purely cheerful person.
But I think she actually has
a lot of depth.
She's perceptive and capable too.
I highly recommend Harimu.
"Highly recommend?"
(Harimu, the youngest,
is the sisters' top pick.)
Would you come back
to the jungle for another trip?
Maybe once?
Once?
I think it'd be nice
to come with friends or family.
- It's a great place to actually talk.
- Exactly. People you can talk to...
Here's the thing.
Holding a "Divorce Re-Boot Camp" here.
That's...
That'd be chaos.
That'd be fun.
I think it'd also be good
for couples before marriage.
They could get to know
each other's personalities.
That'd be fun.
(Bukit Lawang is the perfect place
for those with big decisions to make.)
I want to go to the Amazon...
as my team is called AMAZON.
- True.
- I have to live up to the name.
I want to go there
with them at least once.
A mental-strength training workshop.
Totally.
Like I said earlier,
I never really challenged my limits.
I tended to always avoid them.
But hiking mountains,
going into the jungle,
and feeding elephants...
made me feel like
I had pushed past my limits.
So I learned and felt
so much from this trip.
For me,
I had been doubting...
some of my abilities.
- Why?
- How come?
(Surprised)
I was wondering if I was
actually a worthwhile person.
Then Won Ji told me I was
smart for the first time in my life.
You gave me so many compliments,
and it made me
feel like I was actually useful.
You're totally...
I really liked that about this trip.
Feeling like I'm valuable somewhere.
I usually travel a lot,
so I thought I was already
pretty good at packing light.
But I think I've learned how to get
rid of even more unnecessary baggage.
Was there nothing good
about spending time with us?
- What about us?
- What about me?
(The younger sisters want
to hear something from their eldest.)
(Gathering around)
I think I relied on Won Ji every moment.
Really?
Whether we were bargaining,
going somewhere, or buying something,
I relied on you a lot.
But that might have been a burden for you.
Yes, I think it was probably a lot.
I'm totally fine with that.
It's what I always do anyway.
As the oldest one in this group,
the trip is...
Are you crying?
- Seriously?
- Are you?
To be honest...
But you must have had such a hard time.
It's not that.
(Overwhelmed with emotion)
Was it really that hard?
It's not that it was hard.
I'm actually...
not very good at being a leader.
I'm never that kind of person.
(A moment caught
between wanting to lead the trip well,)
But...
(and doubting herself as the oldest.)
But I learned so much from you.
You're totally a natural leader.
You're a hardcore leader.
You're the ultimate leader.
You're at max leader level.
(Thank you.)
(The extroverted younger sisters'
way of comforting her.)
- It really weighed on you, right?
- I think so.
But she really did work hard.
With four people, it's a group.
So you probably felt
a lot of responsibility.
And it was our first trip
with all four of us.
It must've been awkward
and difficult at times.
But I think we each did
our part really well.
- Absolutely.
- That's right.
I'm glad there were four of us.
(Tight hug)
I love the four of us.
- We each have our own role.
- Absolutely.
It's getting hot now.
(The four have grown even closer.)
So we just have to go home
tomorrow, right?
(An awkward feeling suddenly settles in.)
We've finished eating.
Let's talk, play, and then sleep.
- Sounds good.
- Bedtime.
- It's really dark there.
- We shouldn't look out there.
It's really scary there.
Let's use the bathroom before bed.
It was a good time.
It's really scary.
- Do you think you can sleep, Harimu?
- No.
(After spending an even more
bonding night together)
(The older ones go and shower first.)
We have to take care
of ourselves even in the jungle.
Of course we do.
(Sian and Harimu begin
their nighttime skincare routine.)
We need to soothe our skin, especially
after a long day of skin irritation.
This doesn't feel sticky at all,
- and it moisturizes really well.
- I know.
You know how your sleep quality is better,
- when your skincare routine is perfect?
- Exactly.
You have to seal everything
in with a layer of skincare.
We're in the jungle right now.
Can you believe this?
Does the jungle make
our skin more hydrated?
Anyway, we survived.
We survived even the jungle.
- Let's go straight to bed.
- Okay.
And that was our
nighttime skincare routine.
(Sian carries her through
getting ready for bed.)
(After finishing their nighttime skincare,
it's finally time to sleep.)
(Inside the accommodation)
(Gabee is the first one to come in.)
- Let me know if you need any medicine.
- Okay.
(Gabee is already asleep.)
(Sian is also all ready for bed.)
(She slips into the bed beside Gabee.)
(Won Ji and Harimu return
from the bathroom.)
They're already out cold.
(Looking around)
(She fixes the mosquito nets
over Gabee and Sian.)
(Then gets into bed.)
This isn't really doing anything.
(Won Ji's mosquito net
seems a little off.)
(She just lies down.)
Not bad.
If you need to go to the bathroom,
just tell me.
That would be too rude.
No.
Then let's just agree
to do it for each other.
(Rustling)
I really can't see anything.
(The end of Night 7 in the jungle)
Harimu and I came up with a dance.
(Learning the Abra-ca-Empty choreography)
(The center with standout dance line)
(What's this?)
I got it.
No, you didn't.
You didn't. I saw everything.
She seems a little bossy.
She says you're too bossy.
(A special training session
just for Won Ji.)
(The rookie monster's
performance coming soon)
(Check-out day at the jungle camp)
Did you wash your face
and brush your teeth?
No, I didn't.
(The four have grown
much closer overnight.)
We're taking a taxi down.
(A jungle taxi made of connected tubes)
(Back to civilization
on the garlic-bread tube)
That's our first obstacle.
Ten seconds to launch.
Here we go.
(Wobble)
I'm completely soaked.
Even my underwear is soaked.
Ipu.
(Whoosh)
Are you okay, Ipu?
(Serious)
(An unexpected situation arises.)
(Is something wrong with the tube?)
Why is he serious again?
(Will they make it safely
out of the jungle?)
Are you okay, Harimu?
- You're still not feeling well, are you?
- No.
- Oh, no.
- Let me see.
She has a really high fever.
What do we do?
(In the end, filming is halted
and she is taken to the hospital.)
(Harimu developed
a high fever and abdominal pain.)
(It's an unfamiliar sight
from someone normally so full of energy.)
(What on earth happened to her?)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)